Nguyen Minh Quang

Front End Developer

Phone 0942 884 512 Address 139 Duong Van Duong, Tan Quy,

Tan Phu, Ho Chi Minh

E-Mail quangmn2293@gmail.com



Summary

I quitted my job since Feb 2021 after almost 4 years work like a Tester. I feel happy with my job but in the deep down, something is missing. I spend a lot of time to think about it. And finally found my desire is coding not is testing. So, I decided to take risk, start from the zero and want to be a hero. I spend 6 six months to studying, with 12-16h/day. Started with HTML/CSS basic, Javascript, ReactJS, NextJS, CSS library link Bootstrap, Tailwincss. This is small projects i have done

MINT Lala Store:

- Github: https://github.com/quangnm2293/mintlala_20
- Heroku: https://mintlala.herokuapp.com/

Portfolio:

- Github: https://github.com/quangnm2293/Portfolio
- Vercel: https://portfolio-ebon-two.vercel.app/

Skills

HTML-Level: 3/5

CSS3-Level: 4/5

Javascript-Level: 4/5

ReactJS & NextJS-Level: 3/5

Responsive Design & Mobile-First Websites-Level: 4/5

Photoshop/After Effect/Adobe Premiere-Level: 3/5

Experience

2017-05 - 2020-05 Design Verification

Employee at Arrive Technologies Viet Nam

- Define test cases
- · Define automation test-cases, test scripts.
- · Research SONET-SDH, PDH, Pseudo-wire technology.

2020-06 - 2021-02 System Hardware Validation

Employee at INPHI Viet Nam

- · Define test cases.
- Define Automation Test scripts
- · Research PTP 1588, DSP technology.

Education

2011-09 - 2016-05 Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology

· Major: Electrical and Electronic.